towri a toolkit for building native desktop apps with rented web
towri 一个工具包，用于使用租用的 Web
technologies and a lightweight rust back end it allows you to use your favorite
技术和轻量级 rust 后端构建本地桌面应用
javascript framework to design a ui then package it for mac os windows and linux
from a single code base since the dawn of time javascript developers have been
程序 在过去的十年中，javascript 开发人员一直
searching for the perfect way to build cross-platform apps for the last decade
在寻找构建跨平台应用程序的完美方式，
electron has been the leader in this space which provides a back-end in
electron 一直是这个领域的领导者，它提供
node.js and a front-end with the chromium browser the main criticism of
node.js 的后端和chromium 浏览器的前端，主要批评
this approach is that it results in a very large executable file that consumes
这种方法是它会导致一个非常大的可执行文件，这会
a lot of memory on the machine towri takes a different approach by replacing
在机器上消耗大量内存 towri采用不同的方法，将
node.js with rust and chromium with libraries like tau and rye to provide a
node.js 替换为 rust 和 chromium，使用 tau 和 rye 等库来提供
lightweight webview the end result is a smaller bundle size and more efficient
轻量级 webview 最终结果是更小的包大小和更有效的
memory consumption it also takes security very seriously and provides an
内存消耗它还非常重视安全性并提供
isolation pattern to prevent untrusted scripts from accessing the backend from
隔离模式以防止不受信任的脚本访问 来自
a webview the towery api provides a secure way to access native
web 视图的后端 塔式 API 提供了一种安全的方式来访问
functionality like the file system http and system notifications it's secure by
文件系统 http和系统通知等原生功能，默认情况下它是安全的
default and the only way for the front end to call back and code is when the
，前端回调和代码的唯一方法是
developer explicitly allows it to get started install rust nodejs then create
开发人员明确允许它获取开始安装 rust nodejs 然后创建
a new towry app choose your favorite javascript framework to build the front
一个新的 towry 应用程序 选择你最喜欢的JavaScript 框架来构建
end it looks identical to a web project except for the source towry directory
前端 它看起来与 Web 项目相同，除了源 towry 目录
this is the back end for your native desktop app inside of which you'll find
这是你的本地桌面应用程序的后端，你会在其中找到
icons that will be displayed when the app is installed the icons are
安装应用程序时将显示的图标 这些图标
referenced in the tower config file which also contains important
在 tower 配置文件中被引用，该文件还包含重要
information like the bundle identifier as well as build settings for mac os
信息，例如包标识符以及 mac os
windows and linux now the entry point for your back end is in the main.rs file
windows 和 linux 的构建设置，现在后端的入口点位于 main.rs 文件
from here we can customize the experience on the native operating
从这里我们可以通过导入菜单类型来自定义本机操作系统上的体验
system by importing the menu types we can create a custom native menu that
我们可以创建自定义本机菜单 hat
will work seamlessly on all platforms in addition we can define code and rust
将在所有平台上无缝工作，此外，我们可以定义代码和 rust
that can then be invoked from the javascript front end and it has its own
，然后可以从javascript 前端调用它，它有自己的
custom event system that allows complex message passing from the front end to
自定义事件系统，允许复杂的消息从前端传递
the back end and vice versa now in the front end code a variety of native apis
到后端，反之亦然 在前端代码中，
can be accessed with javascript for example we might import right file from
可以使用 javascript 访问各种原生 api，例如，我们可以从文件系统导入正确的文件，
the file system then simply bind that function to the click event on a button
然后简单地将该函数绑定到按钮上的单击事件
and now the app has the ability to create a file on the user's hard drive
，现在应用程序可以在其上创建文件 用户的硬盘驱动器
after that we may want to show a native dialog which we can accomplish with a
之后，我们可能希望显示一个本机对话框，我们可以使用来自高耸 api 的一行代码来完成，并且现在
single line of code from the towering api and access to any api method can be
可以从 tow reconfig 文件中的允许列表中控制对任何 api 方法的访问以
controlled from the allow list in the tow reconfig file now to compile and
进行编译和
build the app run the tow rebuild command this will create an executable
构建应用程序 运行 tow rebuild命令，这将创建一个可执行文件
and the target directory congratulations you just built a high performance native
和目标目录 恭喜您刚刚构建了一个
desktop app that can run on any platform this has been towri in 100 seconds if
可以在任何平台上运行的高性能原生桌面应用程序就像 100 秒内的 towri 如果
you want to see a full tutorial let me know in the comments thanks for watching
你想看一个完整的教程，请在评论中告诉我谢谢观看
and i will see you in the next one
，我会在下一个看到你